Amina Gadjieva

Content Manager, Photographer

Los Angeles, CA aminagadjieva92@gmail.com +79643205263

I consider myself lucky to have so much experience in 3 different fields. Social media marketing, photography and cinematography - this is what I'm passionate about the most. In each field I feel 100% confident and don't consider it as work, because it's so much more than that to me.

Willing to relocate: Anywhere

Work Experience

Social Media/Content/Community Manager

Amaiz Software - London July 2018 to Present

Social Media/Community/Influencer Marketing Manager

Social media

- 1. Lead all SM activities across Facebook, Instagram, LinkedIn, and Twitter
- 2. Schedule and publish posts about Amaiz news in SM on the behalf of Amaiz on a daily basis
- 3. Monitor SM posts mentioning Amaiz and respond in a timely manner or passe questions to Amaiz Customer Care Team if it's needed
- 4. Analyze the performance of SM activities using native reports from Facebook, Instagram, LinkedIn, and Twitter, as well as Google Analytics

Amaiz Community & customer-review platforms

- 1. Lead all activity across the Amaiz community and customer-review platforms such as Trustpilot.com and help the Marketing Team to create engaging content
- 2. Work with online & offline communities where Amaiz has an established identity

Other:

- 1. Stay in sync with other teams such as Customer Care Team, Web Marketing Team, Creative Team, and Corporate Communications & PR Team and be aware of company news and plans
- 2. Collect feedback from users across various channels, and share it with other teams
- 3. Assist the PPC team with writing ads texts
- 4. Monitor comments in the Amaiz blog and passes them to authors in a timely manner
- 5. Answer emails from users on the behalf of Amaiz
- 6. Stay current on new technologies, best practices, and trends in SM
- 7. Write supportive docs

Photographer/Retoucher

Freelance/Self employed October 2010 to Present

I work with a lot of different styles, including fashion, portraiture, acting/model portfolio (my personal favorite one), special events, food and object etc.

- 1. Relevant experience of delivering photography services on a freelance basis
- 2. Profound knowledge of traditional and digital photography techniques, equipments and principles
- 3. Exceptional knowledge of set up and operation of various studio and location lighting systems
- 4. Thorough knowledge of the operating functions and settings of the digital camera (use Canon cameras and equipment mostly)
- 5. Proficient in the techniques of repairing, upgrading and maintaining the camera
- 6. Strong sense of visualization, background decorations and color combinations
- 7. Efficient in the task of developing and editing photographs creatively
- 8. Skilled at communicating with the customers and advising them on photography

Social media/Content Manager

Advertising agency 'Granat Communications' - Saint-Petersburg September 2017 to May 2018

SMM/Content Management

- 1. Created a strong strategy and engaging content plan
- 2. Created content for social media according to a plan
- 3. Draft of primary and extended commercial offers
- 4. Scheduled and publish posts on social media on a daily basis
- 5. Worked on creative shooting scenarios
- 6. Organized and held photo shoots for brands according to guidelines and requirements
- 7. Searched for talented models and actors
- 8. Searched and rented photo studios using my own big database
- 9. Object and food photography, studio shooting, life style shooting
- 10. Managed YouTube content
- 11. Published videos on YouTube
- 12. Photo retouching (Photoshop, Lightroom)

PR

1. Effectively worked with bloggers and influencers

SERM / ORM

- 1. Community Management
- 2. Worked with reviews on forums, turned brand haters into advocates
- 3. Maintained a good reputation of brands through active communication with customers in the network

Social Media/Content Manager

Freelance - Saint-Petersburg October 2013 to June 2017

- 1. Created a content plan and strategy for social media channels that worked
- 2. Effectively maintained and promoted commercial accounts on social media
- 3. Wrote selling articles on various topics (medicine, accounting, construction, fashion, beauty, etc.)
- 4. Wrote SEO-optimized articles
- 5. Translated the world news (English-Russian) according to guidelines and deadlines
- 6. Wrote engaging articles for blogs

Casting Director

Independent film Devil's Ladder March 2014 to October 2014

- 1. Found talented actors and actresses according to the producer's requirements
- 2. Organized and held photo shoots for actors and actresses that represented them in the best way
- 3. Reviewed demo reels and resumes
- 4. Prepared special casting requirements.
- 5. Quickly provided information to self-represented performers and talent agencies.
- 6. Held auditions and picked the most suitable actors for specific roles according to all the requirements and deadlines
- 7. Scheduled callbacks and second auditions.
- 8. Created prioritized lists of parts and possible preferred performers.
- 9. Created a production schedule for supporting and minor performers.
- 10. Recommended actors to directors and producer based on their auditions
- 11. Scheduled appointments for auditions and readings in short notice.
- 12. Effectively field producer in charge of all talent and production staff in the field.
- 13. Reviewed scripts and suggested reasonable changes

Content Manager

City. Travel - Saint-Petersburg April 2012 to October 2012

- 1. Completely filled 'About' section of 400+ hotels in 30+ countries
- 2. Published information on the website
- 3. Translated the hotel descriptions (English-Russian) for the website
- 4. Negotiated with foreign partners when it was needed

Education

BA in Management

Saint-Petersburg State Economic University - Saint-Petersburg April 2011 to May 2016

Skills

social media marketing (6 years), Content creation (6 years), Adobe photoshop (8 years), digital marketing (6 years), copywriting (6 years), Public Relation, Social Media, Castings (3 years), Organizational Skills (3 years), Photography (8 years), Adobe Lightroom (8 years), Google Drive (10+ years), Profoto Studio Lighting Equipment (8 years), SEO (3 years)

Links

https://aminagadjieva.github.io/content-manager/#contact

Certifications/Licenses

School of Photo Art

September 2010 to Present

Since 2010 I work as a photographer (freelance). I provide photographic services in wide variety of areas, including events, fashion, food and object, commercial and portraiture. I also retouch photos using Photoshop and Lightroom.

Assessments

Social Media Skills — Proficient

March 2019

Measures a candidate's ability to create content, communicate online, and build a brand's reputation. Full results: https://share.indeedassessments.com/share_assignment/l3cxpshmolh4nfki

Indeed Assessments provides skills tests that are not indicative of a license or certification, or continued development in any professional field.

Additional Information

Hi! Just a quick note: currently, I'm in Saint-Petersburg (Russia), but ready to move and travel anytime.